omeleto.com 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy | Omeleto

Omeleto Corp. ("Omeleto.com") understands your concern with privacy and the use of your personal information. By browsing through our website, we assure you that we are committed to protecting your personal privacy.

1\. Information Omeleto.com Collects

Omeleto.com collects e-mail addresses of consumers who communicate with us or through our authorized vendors via e-mail. We also collect information on web pages visited and other information that is provided by consumers either on our site or in response to e-mail communications from us.

All information provided by consumers in any of the above-listed ways or otherwise becomes the property of Omeleto.com once received by us and may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Policy.

Browsing on our Website

If you browse through our site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself.

If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the date and time you access our site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our Web site from another Web site, the address of that Web site, as well as additional information related to your visit.

2\. How We Use Your Personal Information

Collected information is used to improve the content of our website, customize the content or layout of our website for individual users, provide services requested, notify users of updates to the site and, subject to the limitations set forth below, to develop new products and services and to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

Special Sections of Our Site

Omeleto.com offers forums on its site. Any information you disclose in these forums is available to all Omeleto.com registered members and may increase the risk of receiving "spam" or unsolicited e-mail from other parties. Be careful and use discretion when disclosing information online.

3\. Cookies

Cookies cannot be used to retrieve data from your hard drive, obtain your e-mail address or obtain sensitive information about you. When a cookie is set, your browser will check it for length, an expiration date, and where it originated. Only Omeleto.com can access the cookies that we set.

Omeleto.com allows our ad service company to set cookies as well. These cookies can "recognize" a consumer by a Unique identifier assigned at the time of the first visit, and may be used to measure site and page visits and browser version number, and browsing activity. This information may be used to better serve and provide advertising content on future visits and web pages viewed during your browser sessions on our websites. These cookies cannot obtain private information like name, e-mail or other personal information, and are not shared with Omeleto.com.

We use a third party tracking service who sets cookies on our site to track visits, page views and click stream behavior. The third party tracking service reports this data to us in aggregate so we can better understand our users and to improve our site. This information is not tied to any individual user.

4\. Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer web site at [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

If we are going to use your personally identifying information in a manner different from that stated in our privacy policy at the time of collection, we will notify you via e-mail. You will have a choice as to whether or not to allow us to use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will revise this policy and update the date displayed at the top of this policy to reflect that the policy has been changed. In some cases we will also e-mail users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

In the event Omeleto.com or its assets are acquired, such as through merger, acquisition or similar event, resulting in a change in ultimate control over customers' personal information (other than through an internal corporate reorganization or similar transaction), customers will be notified promptly of such change. We will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the acquirer of our customers' personal information respects the provisions of this privacy policy, although this may not be possible in certain legal settings (such as bankruptcy).
